You will feel my power!
Darkness Thunder!
Majiha Pink, there is no light \Nof hope remaining for you!
You're wrong!
Behold!
Majiha Purple!
Basashi! Gyuusashi!
Do you still wish to continue?
Give it up!
It's over!
I, Demon King Lukifel, will rule this \Nworld with the darkness of despair.
This is the beginning of \Nthe darkest of nights,
in which I suck up the dreams of \Nall children around the world!
I won't give up.
I won't let you do that.
No matter what happens, I...
We, the Majiha Sisters, will never give up!
Because we believe in the future!
I can feel you, Majiha Purple.
We believe in love!
The light of hope will never disappear.
It's always burning...
...right here!
With my crimson flame...
...I will burn all!
Majiha Fire!
Maji
{\fad(146,684)\an8\b1\fs24\c&H0DEFF3&\3c&H524FA5&\4c&H05EFF4&\t(4484,5234,1 \c&HFEFEFE&\3c&HFEFEFE&\4a&HFEFEFE&)}We Are the\N{\fs32\c&H5700C6&\3c&HFEFDFE&\4c&HDE7AF5&\blur2\t(4484,5234,1 \c&HFEFEFE&\3c&HFEFEFE&\4a&HFEFEFE&)}Majiha Knights!
We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,40,432,49)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,49,432,51)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,51,432,53)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,53,432,55)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,55,432,57)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,57,432,59)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,59,432,61)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,61,432,63)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,63,432,65)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,65,432,67)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,67,432,69)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,69,432,71)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,71,432,73)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
{\fad(653,1)\an8\b1\fs24\c&HBE18EC&\3c&H792DAB&\4c&H5CFED8&\pos(320,20)\clip(200,73,432,80)}We Are the\NMajiha Knights!
Episode 11
Majiha Forever
"Majiha Forever."
When I was little,
the Majiha Sisters were my role models.
Love and friendship, courage and hope...
I believed that if I had those, I could be \Nan awesome magical girl and save the world.
Majiha... Fire.
Of course... there's no \Nway I could ever be one.
I knew my own limitations.
I protected myself by hanging out \Nwith people who were stronger.
A girl who puts on a nice act around boys!!
I talked trash about them \Nbehind their backs,
but when we ended up with a common enemy,
I'd cling to them.
They all did the same thing...
so I didn't have any right to complain.
You've gotta be able to \Nread the room to get by.
What's so wrong about that?
Like I could ever be a magical \Ngirl of love and hope.
I... revived?
When that happened, \NI was sure it was all over.
Where am I?
So falling down here and dying
allowed me to maintain my body \Nheat so I could revive?
Is this a secret dungeon?
Interesting.
Wasn't expecting to find a place like \Nthis in the mountains, though.
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.993%)
►Deliver the goods to Radodorbo
Time remaining: approx. 5 hours
I don't know how far this thing \Ngoes, but if I keep moving,
we should make it!
Dead
Reviving in
Hakozaki Kusue
No... Why?
Come on, wake up!
Please...
I'm begging you!
Please don't die out here!
Crap! I completely spaced \Nout for a second...
Hakozaki Kusue
Dead
Reviving in
Kusue?
I'm completing this garbage quest \Nif it's the last thing I do!
I should've been verifying my direction \Nlike this from the start.
The wind has calmed down a lot.
Honestly, walking is still tiring \Nme out just as much, but still...
Oh, thank God! A village!
It really is a village!
If I can make it there,\NI should be able to borrow
a carriage or sleigh or something \Nthat's faster than walking!
Hang tight, Kusue. \NI'll bring you back in no time!
Yotsuya-kun and Yuka-san \Nare still alive, too.
Almost there... almost there...
If we all keep trying...
You've gotta be kidding me!
Hakozaki Kusue
Dead
Reviving in
Shindou Iu
Dead
Reviving in
Seriously?
Shindou-san...
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.994%)
►Deliver the goods to Radodorbo
Time remaining: approx. 3 hours
She had stopped at one point,
but after that, it seemed like \Nshe was making progress again.
Frankly, I was kinda counting on her.
Now, of all times?
I'll have to go back and try another route.
Damn it.
Damn it!
It's a dead end!
This is beyond impossible!
Crap! An earthquake?!
Oh, come on...
Looks like earthworms here \Neat dirt to survive, too,
just like the ones in our world.
Not only that, but it's moving in \Na direction I haven't gone yet.
It poses no threat.
Given the circumstances, \NI'm damn glad to see it, but...
It's so slow.
What is this guy's speed, anyway?
But I can't get back to the surface now.
All I can do is trust this \Nguy to do the work.
Hey! Could you pick up the pace a little?
I don't have much time!
Hey, nice! Not bad, Wormtarou!
That's a good boy! \NJust keep plowing through!
There's a Jirou?!
Hey! Don't try to take over Tarou's tunnel!
There's no dirt left for \Nyou to eat, anyway!
You want to eat... me?!
m 0 0 l 250 0 l 250 170 l 0 170
[The Majiha Series]
►An anime series that has been running for 11 years.\N\N►Though it's aimed at young girls, it is renowned for\Nits high animation quality. The battle scene with\NKing Lukifel in episode 49 of We Are the\NMajiha Knights, the first encounter with Ouroboros\Nin episode 14 of Go! Majiha Super Express!, and\Nseveral other notable scenes display surprisingly\Nimpressive artwork.
I seriously can't believe this!
How are Yotsuya and I the only \Nones left at a time like this?
Iu-san and Kusue-san's revival \Ngauges are still stuck at zero...
Ugh!
Hakozaki Kusue
Dead
Reviving in
Shindou Iu
Dead
Reviving in
Is this thing even possible?
Yotsuya Yuusuke
Dead
Reviving in
What?!
No way...
Yotsuya Yuusuke
Dead
Reviving in
What is this?
Oh, no...
Both my mind and my body \Nare frozen stiff...
Huh?
I think... I feel relieved?
Oh, I get it.
All this time, I've been wanting \Nan excuse to give up.
I don't want to die,
but no one can complain if everyone \Nelse died before me, right?
And there's no way I can \Nfinish this on my own.
I don't have to push myself any farther.
Wow... Dying the easy way is... so easy...
Look at you, giving up now!
Huh?
Why are you just lying there, Majiha Pink?!
Majiha... Purple?
No, this is a dream.
My dying wish to meet them...
A delusion... A vision in \Nthe guise of a delusion...
Majiha Pink!
You mean... me?
Whenever you watched us all these \Nyears, what did you see?
When the first Majiha Pink was defeated
by King Lukifel's Darkness Thunder in \Nher final episode, what happened next?
I remember.
We...
When the second Majiha Pink was defeated
by Ouroboros's Energy Stream in her \Nfinal episode, what happened next?
I remember.
...give up!
When the third Majiha Pink was defeated
by Gorgon's Stone Eyes in her final \Nepisode, what happened next?
I saw all of them.
...give up!
So I remember it all!
I'll ask you one more time!
When you watched us all these \Nyears, what did you see?
Answer me!
The Majiha Sisters...
...always...
For the love and hope of all \Nchildren around the world...
...stood back up!
With my crimson flame, I will burn all!
Majiha Fire!
Yuka-san...
Quickly, come this way.
I love your smile, Onee-sama.
Tsu... Tsubasa-kyun...
Come on, almost there!
Keep it up!
Fight on!
I know you can do it.
So happy...
I won't give up.
I'm a magical girl... after... all...
If you sleep now, you'll die.
You're a player, right?
I'll give you a ride, if you'd like.
C'mon.
Wow, you're on the fourth stage?
Rotten luck, getting hit with \Nthis snow on your first quest.
Yeah...
So, which way do you want to go?
Oh, right...
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.996%)
►Deliver the goods to Radodorbo
Time remaining: approx. 3 minutes
No way!
We're never gonna make it now!
You're in a hurry?
It can't be!
Okay. Big hurry. Got it.
Better hold on tight, then.
Huh?
We're speeding up!
Wind spirit, Sylphede, lend me your power.
In the name of the magic \Nuser Fahtina! Come, wind!
Huh?!
How's this work for you?
U-Uh... are you a player, too?
Nope, not me.
I'm just a magic user, that's all.
A magic user?
Come, wind!
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.996%)
►Deliver the goods to Radodorbo
Please! We're so close!
Wind, bestow your blessing upon this hero!
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.996%)
►Deliver the goods to Radodorbo
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.997%)
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.998%)
►Deliver the goods to Radodorbo
►Traverse 5% of the map (currently 4.999%)
Huh? N-No way... We're alive?
Wait, what happened there at the end?
Who finished the quest?
You're kidding!
Yuka-san!
Th-This is...
my chance to take all \Nthe credit for myself!
If I make them owe me one now...
Excellent wor.
Damn it! Don't show up behind me!
As your reward for completing the \Nquest, you may ask one question.
Why is one question all I get for \Neverything I just went through?!
Is that your question?
No, no! Gimme a second!
Now that I think about it,
the quest might have been set up so that \Ngirl would bail me out at the last minute...
We were seriously just seconds from death.
Who was that magic user?
No, I won't ask that. \NI can't waste this question.
This world...
This world is actually virtual...
like, virtual reality, right?
Parallel worlds.
There is a concept by that na.
Parallel worlds?
Say, for example, \Nthat there is an intersection,
Parallel World
Reality\NObserved World
and there is a you who \Nfollows the right path...
as well as a you in a world based on \Ndifferent possibilities who goes left.
The you in the world based on different \Npossibilities who goes left
exists in a parallel wor.
Time
{\an8\fnTimes New Roman\fs16\b1\c&HCE6A18&\3c&HB3FFFA&\bord.25\blur.5\shad0\4c&HDF9E45&\pos(506,80)}Future←                →Past
For that reason, \Nevery time we make a decision,
the potential number of parallel worlds in \Nthe universe increases in a branching struc.
{\fad(484,1)\c&HF0DA8E&\fnArial\b1\fs16\shad0\bord.25\an5\frz270\blur1\3c&HB3FFFA&\pos(70,180)}Number of Parallel Worlds
I guess that does make logical sense.
Now, what if the me who went \Nleft died in an accident?
In a parallel world, I would not have di.
So what if that decision was made not \Ntoday, but three years from now?
Among the parallel worlds,
there would exist a world in \Nwhich I died in an accid.
And what if the decision was an action \Ntaken by your parents twenty years ago?
Among the parallel worlds,
there would be one in which \Nyour parents died twenty years ag.
Nonexistent
Naturally, that means \Nyou would not be born.
In this way, parallel worlds become \Nmore and more unrealistic
the farther they branch out from \Nthe past from which they origina.
This branching
has been repeating eternally \Nsince the birth of the univer.
Does that mean the number of parallel \Nworlds is basically infinite?
We are capable of using special methods
to observe and travel between parallel \Nworlds that meet a certain conditio.
The condition is that the worlds \Nexist on a similar wavelength.
Which means that world is...
a world that branched off \N4.6 billion years ago,
where a sentient race identical \Nto humans came to exist
and lived through a history \Nsimilar to human history.
It is an Earth based on different possibil.
What does that mean?!
You do not have the right to ask a ques.
Of course, the name of the planet, \Nthe things it is made of,
and its terrain are diff.
But it is not a virtual realit.
It is a planet that exists in the same \Nplace as Earth in a parallel wor.
If anything, you are the only things \Nin this world that are virtu.
We're virtual?
Well, I guess if we weren't, \Nwe couldn't come back from the dead.
True.
Which means all of the \Nother things there...
the sky, the seas, the land,
the creatures living there, \Nand the humans...
are all perfectly real, \Nflesh-and-blood beings in realit.
So the people in this \Nworld aren't virtual...
They're Earthlings that just \Nexist in a parallel reality?
I... killed real people...
Subquest\N\NTransform into Majiha!
Turn into Majiha charact!
King Deokk! I will avenge Bihmsberg!
Majiha Knight...
...Illumination!
With my crimson flame, I will burn all!
Majiha...
Miracle Fire!
Just a dream...
If only a Majiha would come to me now...
You called?
Not for you!